const questions = [
  {
    question: "1. What kind of food is a yam?",
    answers: [
      "Fruit",
      "Vegetable",
      "Mango",
      "Juice"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1
  },
  {
    question: "2. How many species of yams are found around the world?",
    answers: [
      "20",
      "50",
      "400",
      "600"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3
  },
  {
    question: "3. Which continent produces the most yams?",
    answers: [
      "Africa",
      "Asia",
      "North America",
      "UC Irvine"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "4. Which is these is NOT a possible color of the inside of a yam?",
    answers: [
      "White",
      "Orange",
      "Yellow",
      "Purple"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1
  },
  {
    question: "5. What season are yams usually harvested in?",
    answers: [
      "Spring",
      "Summer",
      "Fall",
      "Winter"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "6. Which vitamin are yams NOT a major source of?",
    answers: [
      "Vitamin A",
      "Vitamin B",
      "Vitamin C",
      "Potassium"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0
  },
  {
    question: "7. In Ghana, yams are traditionally served to celebrate what?",
    answers: [
      "AntAlmanac and Zotistics joining PeterPortal",
      "Mars starting work at Cameo",
      "Ryan stealing Patrick's Igloo",
      "The arrival of a new baby"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3
  },
  {
    question: "8. What food item are yams usually confused with?",
    answers: [
      "Bananas",
      "Potatoes",
      "Sweet Potatoes",
      "Taro"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2
  },
  {
    question: "9. For how long have people been cultivating yams?",
    answers: [
      "2,000 years",
      "10,000 years",
      "100,000 years",
      "Since the start of time"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1
  },
  {
    question: "10. Which is NOT a health benefit of yams?",
    answers: [
      "Heals skin diseases",
      "Cures respiratory problems",
      "Aids digestion",
      "Improves eyesight"
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3
  },
];

export default questions;
